socialappshq.com 2013-12-07

# Social Media Marketing Made Really Simple - SocialAppsHQ

Last Updated: Jan 1, 2011

Your privacy is important to Shimply Software Pvt. Ltd., Inc. (DBA SocialAppsHQ). This privacy policy ("Policy") applies to the SocialAppsHQ Web sites ("Sites") and SocialAppsHQ applications such as those built on popular social networking sites ("Applications"). This Policy explains how your personal information is collected, used, and disclosed by SocialAppsHQ.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED**  
We collect information from you in various ways when you use our Sites and Applications. We may collect personal information you directly provide on our Sites. In addition, we may collect personal information from you as a user of our Applications. Information we may collect includes name and email address, demographic information such as gender, education, birth date, preferences, and interests, and any other information requested from you. We may supplement this information with information collected from other companies.

In addition, when you visit our Sites some information may be automatically collected. For example, it is standard for your Web browser to automatically send information to every Web site you visit including ours. That information includes your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, access times, browser type and language, and referring Web site addresses. We may also collect information about your computer's operating system and information about your usage and activity on our Sites.

Cookies.  
We may automatically collect certain information through the use of "cookies." Cookies are small data files that are stored on your hard drive by a Web site. Among other things, the use of cookies helps us to improve our Sites and your experience. We use cookies to see which areas and features are most popular, to count the number of computers accessing our Sites, to personalize your experience, and to remember your preferences. If your browser is set not to accept cookies or if you reject a cookie, you may not be able to access certain features or services of our Sites.

Web Beacons.  
Web beacons, also known as gifs, are electronic images that may be used on our Sites or in our emails. A Web beacon may be used on our Web pages to collect information, deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness, or in our emails to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.

**USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
We use your personal information to provide you with services, to operate and improve our Sites and Applications, to send you messages, and for other purposes described in this Policy or disclosed to you on our Sites or in connection with our services. For example, we may use the information we collect from you on our Sites and Applications:  
• to personalize and improve your experience on our Sites and with our Applications;  
• to respond to comments and questions and provide customer service;  
• to deliver service messages and other services and content you request and to send information related to accounts and services, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;  
• to send you information about new promotions, products, and services offered by SocialAppsHQ and our selected partners; and  
• to conduct an aggregated analysis of the performance of promotions.

Personal information you provide may be linked or combined with other personal information we collect or obtain from third parties. We match your information, in part, to help understand your needs and provide you with better service.

SocialAppsHQ may store and process personal information in the United States and other countries.

**SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
Some promotions and features of our Sites and Applications are presented jointly with other companies. If you choose to participate in those promotions or use those features, your information may be collected and used by SocialAppsHQ and those other companies. Use of your information by those other companies for their own purposes is not controlled by SocialAppsHQ and is subject to their own terms and privacy policies. Please review each sponsor's promotion rules and privacy policy for details.

We do not share your personal information with third parties other than as described above and as follows:  
• with your consent, for example, when you agree to our sharing your information with other third party partners for their own marketing and other purposes subject to their separate privacy policies;  
• with third party vendors, consultants and other service providers ("Service Providers") who are working on our behalf and need access to your information to carry out their work for us;  
• to (a) comply with laws or respond to lawful requests and legal process, (b) to protect the rights and property of SocialAppsHQ, our agents, members, and others including to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of use, or (c) in the good faith belief that disclosure is needed to respond to an emergency or protect the personal safety of any person; and  
• in connection with any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company. In any such event, we will provide notice if your data is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

**SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
SocialAppsHQ takes reasonable security measures to protect your personal information to prevent loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are impenetrable.

If you use a password on our Site, you are responsible for keeping it confidential. Do not share it with any other person. If you believe your password has been misused, please advise us immediately.

**CHOICES ABOUT USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**  
You may "opt-out" of receiving promotional emails from SocialAppsHQ by following the instructions in those emails. You may also send requests relating to promotional messages and your permission for sharing information with third parties for their marketing purposes by emailing [privacy@SocialAppsHQ.com](mailto:privacy@SocialAppsHQ.com). Opt-out requests will not apply to transactional service messages, including messages about your current SocialAppsHQ account and services.

You may also choose to remove the Application from your Facebook account by clicking on "Settings" in the toolbar and selecting "Application Settings" from the drop-down menu. Click the "x" next to the Application's name, then click "remove" again to confirm the deletion.

**UPDATING AND ACCESSING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
If your personal information changes, we invite you to correct or update your information as soon as possible. You can request changes or access to your information by emailing [privacy@SocialAppsHQ.com](mailto:privacy@SocialAppsHQ.com).

**CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**  
SocialAppsHQ may change this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the "Last Updated" date above. If there are material changes to this policy, we will notify you more directly. We encourage you to review this Policy whenever you visit our Sites or use our Applications to understand how your personal information is used.

**QUESTIONS ABOUT THIS POLICY**  
If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at [privacy@SocialAppsHQ.com](mailto:privacy@SocialAppsHQ.com).
